

### Hello!

I'm Evgeniya Chernyavskaya.

I'm 40. At the moment I live in Bendery, Moldova.

I love traveling and try not to miss the opportunity to see something new. I want to become a programmer and start my journey as a front-end developer.

## Short history about me

- "When you think it's too late, the truth is, it's still early"
- "Whether you think you can or think you can't, you're right"

I have worked in the power industry all my life. I climbed the career ladder from engineer to chief engineer, but at the age of 40 I decided to change my life and start everything from scratch. I want to change the field of work and become an IT developer. I think my previous work experience will help me achieve my goal in a short time. Assembled, balanced, competently organize the workflow. I have experience in personnel management. I know how to focus on the task at hand to achieve the result. I have a high capacity for work and an analytical mindset.

#### **Skills**

"You know nothing till you prove it"

# Professional at old job:

- Project Management
- Personnel Management
- Workflow Automation
- Business Process Modeling
- Production planning
- Persistence in completing tasks

### Personal:

- Communicative
- Teamwork
- Time Management
- · Analytical Skill
- Multitasking
- Stress Tolerance
- Attentiveness
- Forethought

## Professional:

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript

#### **Education**

"Education is not Preparation For Life, Education is Life Itself."

"Education is not the leaning of facts, but the training of the mind to think. Education is a gift that none can take away. I am still learning every day."

- Pridnestrovian State University T.G. Shevchenko. Faculty of Engineering and Technology. Electrical Engineer. 1999-2004
- IT-Academy of Alexey Sukhorukov. Web development. 2019
- Excel Academy. Excel advanced features and macros. 2020
- Excellent Online School Statistics. Visual Reporting Wizard in Excel. 2021
- Result.School. HTML & CSS is the first step to becoming an IT developer. 2022

### **Employment**

OOO "MONTEL"		
Design Engineer	Head of Department	Chief Engineer
02.2011 - 11.2016	11.2016 - 05.2021	05.2021 - 04.202

Name: Chernyavskaya Evgeniya Email: chernyavskaya\_ev@mail.ru

+373 788 66 917 Phone:

<sup>&</sup>quot;Whenever you want to achieve something, keep your eyes open, concentrate and make sure you know exactly what it is you want. No one can hit their target with their eyes closed. To accomplish great things we must not only act, but also dream, not only plan, but also believe."